[keys jangle]
♪ Oh, Danny boy ♪
♪ The pipes ♪
♪ The pipes are calling ♪
♪ From Glen to Glen ♪
♪ And down the mountainside ♪
♪ The summer's gone ♪
♪ And all the roses falling ♪
♪ 'Tis you ♪
♪ 'Tis you must go ♪
♪ And I must bide ♪♪
[male #1]
'Thank you.'
Which one's ours?
The one who looks like
she blows her nose
with $100 bills.
They all look like that.
Joke. That's her over there.
Let's go.
We shouldn't have
to be asking for charity.
The department needs
the money. Smile.
[ominous music]
[crackling]
Mrs. Doverton. Hi.
I'm Teresa Lisbon.
This is Kimball Cho.
We're with the CBI.
You're sponsoring us
for the event, I believe.
Oh, yes, of course. Yes.
Well, welcome.
I was very sorry to hear
about your terrible loss.
Umm, you know,
those agents.
Thank you.
I can only imagine what
you must all be feeling.
We don't talk about it.
Thanks.
[beeps]
[rapid beeping]
[cranking]
Well, I'd like to
introduce you to my nephews.
- Uh, this is Thomas.
- Hi.
Say hello, Thomas.
Please call me Tom.
- And this is George.
- So, Miss Lisbon..
What entertainment do you have
planned for us this evening?
Actually, a member of our team
used to be in show business.
He's sort of a magician
and he's going to entertain us,
hopefully, yeah.
[indistinct conversations]
How nice.
Cheers.
[heavy breathing]
[indistinct chattering]
What?
Just a smile.
He just smiled.
[male #2]
'Ladies and gentleman. Please
welcome Mr. Patrick Jane.'
'of the California Bureau
of Investigation.'
Good evening.
You're a very
good looking crowd.
Thank you for coming this
evening. You too, back there.
'You look very regal
up there in the window.'
My name is Patrick Jane.
I'm from the CBI.
Uh, this is an egg.
Yes. I'm supposed to do magic
tricks and read minds for you
but, after some thought,
I, uh..
decided, what the hell.
I don't really want to do
that corny old stuff, so..
[crowd cheers]
Well..
Instead what I'd like
to do is much cooler.
I would like to transform
your consciousness.
Have any of you ever stopped
to consider what lucky bastards
you all are.
If you think the suffering
and the injustice in the world.
Every second of every day
there is someone, somewhere
'crying out in pain and fear.'
'A woman is raped.
A child starves to death.'
'A man is executed
for a crime he didn't commit.'
'But, here we are.'
'We could be standing on a roof
in some Bangladeshi village'
'waiting for
the flood waters to recede.'
No!
[gunshots]
But no, here we are
in this lavish ballroom..
...sipping
French champagne and..
declining
the hors d'oeuvres.
Thank you very much. Yes.
Put your hands in the air
anyone that feels lucky.
If you think you are lucky,
put your hands up.
That's right.
We here are all blessed
by fortune.
'If you disagree,
put down your hands.'
'If you don't think
you need to express your thanks'
for that blessing,
put down your hand.
[indistinct conversations]
'If you're not willing
to write a check'
that will save actual lives,
then please put down your hand.
That's great.
Very good.
Okay. Now, magic.
You sir, put your left hand
in your jacket pocket
and take out
whatever is in there
and show it to everybody.
[chirping]
'Thank you. Thank you.'
[applause continues]
Make those checks legible.
A novel way of raising money,
I must say.
Ah, well, the direct approach
is sometimes the best.
Oh, do excuse me.
You son of a bitch.
You scared the crap out of me.
Oh, please, like I don't know
how to work
a fat crowd of suckers.
Why, yes.
What?
No.
Oh, my god.
What is it?
What's-what's the matter?
Carl's been shot.
[theme music]
[police siren blaring]
[Teresa]
'Whoever it was,
they were thorough.'
They bypassed
the alarm system somehow.
Shut off the security cameras.
Prints are unlikely.
'When was the last time
you changed the lock code?'
That was a class five
B vault door.
And I was told that no one
could get through it.
Insurance had damn well
better pay.
A good safecracker
can get through anything
with the right tools
and enough time.
This is beautiful.
Look at that.
Excuse me.
Would you stop that, please?
Sure. No problem.
Just havin' a look.
Got some cool stuff in here.
Very cool.
You two are brothers, right?
Indeed.
It's nice to see that the case
is in such perceptive hands.
Can hands be perceptive?
I don't think so.
So is it usual that your uncle
is here after closing?
He's not our uncle exactly.
Oh, I'm sorry. Uh, the man
having sex with your aunt, then.
No.
No, but tonight was the benefit.
Carl must have forgotten
something and come back
and surprised the thieves.
Hmm. Sure did.
[Patrick]
'What's the deal with Carl
and your aunt?'
'How did they get together?'
They met, uh,
four years ago at the club.
The labor day
senior tennis tournament.
He was a pro back east.
And they married and he joined
the family business?
Yes, that's correct.
Does your resentment of him,
uh, create any tension?
What resentment?
Well, the old girl gets laid.
Next thing you know,
you got a new business partner.
Come on. You resent him.
No.
Carl's been a godsend,
actually.
A natural salesman,
and he's made Esther very happy.
Yes, that's-that's
the main thing.
If I may say so,
what I do very much resent
is the tone
of your questioning.
I'm sorry
if we've offended you.
No, don't say that.
This is a murder investigation.
I can be as hardass
as I'd like to be. Thank you.
Actually, it's
not a murder investigation yet.
If Mr. Ward dies,
which seems likely
it'll become
a murder investigation.
- Oh. Yeah, well, that's right.
- Yeah.
He's not dead.
Uh, well, uh, I apologize
for my rudeness.
Let's go.
Okay.
[female #1]
'We got a break
in the case, Boss.'
This is last night's footage
from a parking lot camera
across the street.
That's Doverton & Co.
Back there on the right.
Okay, so now we zoom in
like this and..
...there. That's him.
Then I checked
the new intersection cameras
the city put in to catch
traffic light violations.
I figured I'd look at the ones
nearest to Doverton's
around that time of night.
Car's registered
to Doyle Murphy.
His sheet's a mile long
and safecracking was
his specialty.
I got a current address
in Locke.
Nice work, Van pelt. Quick.
It's your hook. Contact local
PD. And have them pick him up.
- Take Rigsby with you.
- Thanks, boss.
It's all very neat and easy.
Hey, sometimes it happens
that way.
Yeah. I'll take a layup anytime,
thank you.
Well, you guys are
the professionals here.
But is it usual, there is
a single perpetrator
for this kind
of a jewelry heist?
No, at least two.
Sometimes maybe three or four.
Then there's the timing
of the robbery.
Weren't those diamonds
supposed to be picked up
the next morning?
Yeah, 10:15.
Right when they opened.
Gee, you think
maybe it's an inside job?
Uh, yes, I do.
Yeah, well, guess what?
We're way ahead of you.
Because we're doin'
background checks
on the whole
Doverton staff list.
My provisional bet,
provisional, Carl Ward.
Hello. He was shot three times.
- Best accomplice is a dead one.
- Well, he's not dead.
Nobody's perfect.
That's it. Carl ward is crooked
because he got shot.
- He's an ex-tennis pro.
- So?
Shady people,
by definition, disappointed.
Should be on center court,
Wimbledon.
Instead he's tossing lobs
to rich old ladies.
- Makes him bitter and twisted.
- Case closed.
I'm just saying.
Go talk to Murphy.
See what he has to say about it.
I'm just sayin'.
Jane knows about us.
I'm sure he does.
Why would it be so bad if people
figured out we're together?
Because...What do you mean, why?
I just mean, is this it?
What? Here? This building?
No, no. I mean us.
Is this all it's gonna be
sneaking around all the time,
afraid someone's gonna find out?
No, it's just the bureau rules.
The rules are the rules, right?
Maybe I'm sick of the rules.
That she blows.
[car door closes]
You don't wanna
to talk about it, huh?
No, I do, just not here,
not on the job.
We'll have to talk
about it sometime.
Yeah. Soon.
CBI.
I'd like to know about
the, uh, resident
who owns the blue beater there.
Murphy? Pays his rent,
makes no trouble.
What'd he do?
Has he had any visitors
recently?
No. Oh, wait.
Yeah, couple of hours ago.
Big guy in a cowboy hat.
Pimped out truck.
Stayed...five minutes,
split.
Does murphy's room have any
rear exit of any kind? A window?
Nope.
What did he do?
Mr. Murphy?
State agents.
We need to talk to you.
Mr. Murphy?
[door creaks]
Go.
Clear.
Guess that lets Carl Ward
off the hook then, huh?
Ballistics owes me,
expedited the report.
This gun was used to shoot
both Doyle Murphy and Carl Ward.
There were no jewels
in the room or the car.
No prints on the gun.
Start going through all
of Murphy's known associates.
We're looking for a cowboy
in a fancy truck.
Kind of a thin trail.
Murphy's a career criminal.
He has a lot of associates.
Hmm.
- Maybe I can help.
- Just maybe?
Feeling unsure about yourself,
are you?
Don't let one wrong hunch
throw you.
Well, A, we don't know yet
that I'm wrong about Ward.
And B, bring
the motel desk clerk in.
Maybe he can recall a little
more detail than he thinks
about this cowboy.
[Patrick]
'Can you see him?'
Yes.
'What's he doing?'
He's getting out
of the truck.
And he's walking across
the forecourt to Murphy's room.
Can you read the license plate
on the truck?
No.
Look closer.
No, I can't. It's blocked.
What's he wearing?
Cowboy hat, brown.
Black jeans.
Sunglasses, Aviator style.
That's very good, Marty.
What else can you see?
He's wearing a t-shirt
with a Bulldog on the front.
'under it, true blue.'
[indistinct conversations]
[instrumental music]
[dog barks]
Donald Culpepper?
Who the hell are you?
Tsst. Quiet.
I have reason to believe that
you visited with Doyle Murphy
at the Starlite motor court.
Is that correct?
That's partially correct.
I went to see him.
He wasn't there, so I left.
Why'd you go see him?
Social visit. Catchin' up.
He was married to my sister.
We have sad news.
Your ex-brother-in-law is dead.
I'm in shock.
How'd that happen?
He was shot. Any idea
who might want to do that?
No.
How about you?
I have nothing but love
for Murph.
Why would you think
otherwise?
Well, because we read
your rap sheet.
You're a professional criminal
implicated in several murders.
I'm a dynamic businessman
who pushes the envelope.
Anybody can imply anything. It's
another thing to make it stick.
Yeah. Get out.
We need to continue
this conversation downtown.
Thanks.
I deduce from the irritated tone
of your phone conversation
that I was right
about Carl Ward.
Half right.
Go on.
His real name's
Carl Wysowcki.
He was in jail
for kiting checks.
He's got an ex-wife
in Bayonne, New Jersey.
She's owed $90,000
in back alimony.
Half?
So he changed his name.
What of it?
Did you know about
the jail time?
Yes, of course I did.
And the ex-wife?
Of course.
He told me everything.
Hmm, liar.
- Bad liar.
- How dare you.
Well, it's a compliment
to your good character.
You'd rather be a good liar?
Hmm?
I knew everything
about Carl's past.
We're glad he told you, ma'am
because we have to consider
the possibility that he was
somehow involved in the jewel
heist and double-crossed.
His honesty with you makes him
far less of a suspect.
Do you have anything further?
My husband needs me.
No, ma'am. Thank you.
- How's he doing?
- He'll live.
They were going to bring him
out of sedation tomorrow.
Excellent.
[Cho]
'Why did you visit with
Doyle Murphy?'
I didn't. He wasn't home.
If he had been home,
what would you have said to him?
Gimme my money.
- He owed you. How much?
- 200 grand and change.
He comes out of incarceration
this last bit he did
and needed to go into rehab.
Junkie son of a gun was there
over a month on my dime.
That's very generous of you.
Nah. What am I gonna do?
At the time,
this was two years back
he's married to my sister.
Moron.
Then he kicks your sister
to the curb
after some
domestic violence problems.
And he still owes you 200 grand.
One, my sister
is a goblin shark.
Freakin' Gandhi would take
a pop at her.
I got no beef with Doyle
over that, believe me.
And two, this money
is what I'm telling ya.
Why would I kill a guy who
owes me that much money?
Because he just made
a very big score.
- Is that right?
- Yes, it is.
Maybe you decided to take
what was owed to you
and a little bit more.
What score is this?
Doverton's?
- You heard about that.
- Was on the TV. Nice work.
Doyle did that? Wow.
Did you ever own a Beretta 950?
As a matter of fact, I did
use to have one of those.
I didn't like the balance.
I sold it to Doyle, why?
Hmm.
Well, I don't care what you're
gonna say. I like him for it.
What do you mean, you don't
care what I have to say?
He's obvious, so you're gonna
say he's not the guy
because, that would be boring.
No, he looks good for it.
Superficially, at least.
I was merely gonna state
that we need to find a link
between him and Doyle
and someone inside Doverton's.
I thought Carl Ward
was your man on the inside.
No. I-I noted
that he was a tennis pro
and extrapolated
from there.
No. No, you said
he was the guy.
Well, if you recall--
Guys. I mean, Boss.
I think I found the link
you're talking about.
The old footage from
the store's security cameras
is saved on a hard drive
off-site.
I figured if Murphy
had been casing the store
I could find him
on the old footage.
- Who's that?
- I'll enhance it.
[keys click]
[Patrick]
'Hmm. Wow.'
Tom Doverton.
It's a customer, I guess.
I'm talking to a customer.
That's the man
who robbed your family store
and shot your uncle.
Are you sure
you don't know him?
Because you're talking
like you're old friends.
No. I'm just helpin' a customer
with their purchase. That's all.
And you've never seen
that man before?
No.
And you don't know
the name Doyle Murphy?
No.
The kid's aunt and brother
are here with a lawyer.
Darn. We haven't gotten
anywhere with him yet.
You want me to stall 'em?
It's best just to cut him loose.
He's denying everything anyway.
Unless we can make
some connection
to Culpepper and Doyle, we've
got nothing to hold him on.
Okay.
You go and ask Culpepper about
Tom, I'll deal with the family.
You can take Tom home now.
We just had a couple of
questions, we needed to ask him.
What questions?
I'm sure, he'll fill
you in on the details.
Well, I'd appreciate it
if next time you wish
to speak to a member of my
family, you call me first.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
That's not our practice.
Can I walk you
to the elevator?
[instrumental music]
You do know why I'm letting
you go, don't you?
Let me guess.
I'm innocent.
[Patrick chuckles]
No, I figured
you're stupid.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
Either you really didn't know
that Doyle was gonna
actually rob
the jewelry store..
...stupid innocent.
Or you did know
and you're gonna lead us
to a clue.
Stupid guilty.
You should be more careful
how you talk to people.
Yeah, figure I'm
pretty safe here.
I mean, what are you
gonna do?
You think I care
where we are?
Go ahead.
Do something, you miserable
little sadist.
Hello, Lisbon. Hi, Dovertons.
What's going on, Jane?
I'm just letting
Mr. Culpepper go.
We don't need him
for anything, do we?
- Do we?
- Sometime.
When you least expect it..
...I'll find you.
- You, uh..
- Wait for the next one.
Alright.
So long, partner.
Happy trails.
Okay, what the hell was that?
- What was what?
- Letting Donny Culpepper go.
You have no right, whatsoever,
to make those kind of decisions.
Well, you weren't
gonna keep him here.
On what? For what?
He wasn't gonna talk. Be honest.
I could have held him
on the weapons charge.
- Oh, please!
- Stop.
There's principle involved.
Don't think I don't know
what you're doing.
What're you talking about?
Showing the Dovertons to Donny
Culpepper. You wanted to see
if he recognized
one of them, didn't you?
You watch too much TV. I just
thought there was no reason
to keep Donny Culpepper here.
Now that's just annoying.
You're not even putting
any effort into the lie.
Hey, boss. Coroner's here.
She got something to show us.
[instrumental music]
Well...it's really beautiful.
Mm?
I found it in Doyle Murphy's
lower intestine.
My supposition is that he
swallowed it
in an attempt to get a larger
share of the loot
before it was divided
with any partners.
Yeah, I guess Murphy
misread that situation, huh?
Did you find anything else
surprising in there?
- Other than that?
- Just that.
[colleagues shrieking]
What the hell was that?
Uh, I..
[Jane clears throat]
...had a hunch
that it was a fake.
- Guess I'm wrong about that.
- Uh, yeah.
Where is it?
Well, the good news is
it's not out there.
So it's in here somewhere.
I'll find it.
Anyone see a little, uh..
[imitates ricocheting sound]
Nope?
There's gotta be a connection
between Doyle Murphy
and Tom Doverton.
Yeah, but w-what was it?
What would bring
those two together?
They have nothing in common.
- What are you guys looking for?
- A diamond.
What did he do?
Hit it with a fire extinguisher.
- Of course.
- I got it!
Oh, thank God.
Where was it?
No, I got
where Doyle and Tom connect.
- Doyle was in rehab.
- Yes.
And Tom Doverton does
look the rehab type.
Van Pelt, find out where Doyle
went to rehab. Keep looking.
Don't worry.
This is justice department.
- Who's gonna steal it here?
- You be quiet!
[muttering indistinctly]
Windward Clarity has the highest
ratio of staff-to-patient
of any facility
in the state.
Our philosophy mixes
traditional western practices
with spiritual aspects
of the East.
Now, may I ask which one of you
needs our help
or is it both of you?
- Actually, we just wanted--
- It's her.
- No.
- Oh, darling, please.
Can we, just this once, do it
my way? Just once.
Thank you.
In the beginning,
it was just social but..
...well, more recently..
...it's been starting
to worry both of us.
Right, darling?
Right this way.
I'll introduce you to one of our
intake specialists.
Fantastic.
Oh, uh, that's the office.
I'm gonna have to take this.
Uh, baby, you go ahead,
take a look.
I'll be five minutes.
I'll be right there.
Look after her.
I'm very proud of you.
- I understand your nervousness.
- I love you.
[Dr. Joseph]
'It's completely natural.'
'But you've already taken
the first step in recognizing..'
[telephone ringing]
[instrumental music]
Our kitchen is capable
of preparing food for any diet.
And of course, we have a pair
of on-site nutritionists.
Um, your husband is
taking quite a long time.
You should understand...
he's not really my husband.
Oh, that's quite alright.
We're not judgmental about such
things here.
That's not what I mean.
Whoa.
Uppers and Downers.
Uppers and..
...you're so rock 'n' roll,
doctor.
That is private material.
Doctor-patient privilege
is sacrosanct.
Yes, I know.
That's why we did it this way.
This is a murder investigation.
We can be as hard-ass
as we want. I found it..
...the, uh, patient roster
for the first two weeks
of Doyle Murphy's stay.
Guess who his acting sponsor was
when he first arrived?
- Tom Doverton?
- No!
- George.
- The brother?
Yeah.
I will be calling
your superiors.
You know, a lot of people say
that to me
and you know what I say?
- I say--
- Let's go. Come on.
[rattling pills]
Get some help, doc.
That stuff will kill you.
[instrumental music]
[door creaks]
George isn't here.
He's already left.
He's not guilty, you know.
How'd you know we were coming?
The director
of the clinic called.
He told us what you'd done.
George was in rehab
with Doyle Murphy, that's true.
But that's all that it was.
So you're saying if we dig,
we won't find any more contact
between George and Doyle?
He came into the store.
A guy like that
at Doverton & Company, I mean..
Come on.
If my aunt found out..
We need to talk to George.
- He's gone.
- Oh, really?
Uh, I think he's hiding
behind the door.
George?
George, come out.
I'm sorry, Tom.
You were just trying
to help.
but we both know
there's no..
...hiding from something
like this.
I had nothing to do
with the robbery
or Doyle Murphy's murder.
I only lied to protect
my aunt from..
...the shame of my addiction.
Tom, call Dicky Purcell.
Tell him to..
...meet me
at the CBI offices.
- Yeah.
- After you.
Excuse me.
Do you work here?
Uh, certainly, sir.
Um, how can I help you?
My wife...it's her birthday.
Of course. Of course.
Uh, Michelle?
Michelle here, would be happy
to help you.
Thank you.
- Mr. Doverton?
- Yeah.
I need a signature
for this.
There you go.
What?
"You'll get a call in 2 hours.
"Take the jewels
where you are told.
No cops or your aunt dies."
[instrumental music]
She's gone.
Oh, God.
Why would anybody kidnap
Aunt Esther?
Someone thinks your brother was
partners with Doyle Murphy.
Well, you think so.
Why shouldn't everyone else?
Donny Culpepper?
What? Who's Donny Culpepper?
You saw him when we were
waiting for the elevator.
Doyle Murphy owed him
a lot of money.
He might think that that debt
transfers with the diamonds.
Okay, but we don't have
the diamonds.
Well, he doesn't know that.
Well, you have to go
arrest him right away.
That's what we're trying to do,
Mr. Doverton.
Agent Van Pelt is working with
local police as we speak.
- We're pursuing several leads.
- But the note says no police.
Well, it's a little late
for that.
Whoa. What are you gonna do? How
are you gonna get our aunt back?
We'll do everything we can
to find her.
In the meantime, when the
kidnappers call, you have to try
and stall them.
- Take that.
- Okay.
Okay.
- It's almost time. You ready?
- Yeah, ready.
- And you?
- I don't know.
Just stay calm.
Keep the kidnapper on the line
and keep him calm.
Remember, keep going
as long as you can, okay?
[phone vibrating]
- Headphones?
- Yeah, in the other room.
Ready?
Here we go.
Hello?
[distorted voice]
'Do you have the jewels ready?'
[no audio]
How do I know
you have my aunt?
- I-I demand to--
- No.
[kidnapper]
'You don't demand anything.
You shut up and you listen.'
I-I-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- I-I just need proof before--
- Proof?
[kidnapper]
'I'll give you proof.'
[Esther]
'Hello? George?'
Esther, are you alright?
[kidnapper]
'There. That's your proof.'
'If you want to see her
alive again'
'you're gonna bring me
the diamonds.'
I-I-I...I can't do that.
- I-I...
- Got him.
[kidnapper]
'You think this is
some kind of a game?'
No! No. I-I-I'm sorry.
[kidnapper]
'Are you gonna give me
the jewels?'
I-I...I don't have the jewels.
I'm trying to tell you.
[kidnapper]
'Alright, then.
This is your decision.'
[gunshot]
Aunt Esther!
[kidnapper]
'You're next.
Now, I'm coming for you.'
Oh, my God.
[groans]
Stay right there.
Rigsby!
[vibrates and rings]
[ringing continues]
Hello?
[kidnapper]
'Where are the jewels, Tom?'
- 'We both know you have 'em.'
- They're going to catch you.
They're going to get you
right now.
[kidnapper]
'No, no, no.'
'I'm gonna get you,Tom.'
[kidnapper]
'I know everything
about you.'
[kidnapper]
'Yeah, Doyle Murphy
told me everything.'
Screw you.
I'll give you $50,000..
...$50,000 to leave me
and my brother alone.
[kidnapper]
'Oh, you think
you're so tough.'
[kidnapper]
'You give me what I want, or I
will come and take it from you.'
I'll make it $75,000,
but no more.
I'm not givin' up
the diamonds.
You stupid, rich brat.
You think
you can dictate terms?
Not this time, Tom.
[distorted voice]
'Not this time.'
'I'm gonna make you pay
and pay.'
You try it.
You try it,
and you see what happens.
Tough guy, huh?
You're gonna give me the same
thing you gave to Doyle Murphy?
That's right.
You push me hard enough,
and you'll see.
Okay.
Thanks, Tom. That's great.
We got it all on tape. You're
going down. Give me the phone.
Hands behind your back.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Doyle Murphy.
Let's go.
Like a charm.
Ah, tea.
Lovely.
Ms. Doverton?
I'm sorry, but we've had
to mislead you a little
to solve this crime.
I'm afraid I've got
some difficult news.
Your nephew, Tom, was involved
in the robbery.
Tom?
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
[monitor beeping steadily]
Ahem.
Oh, hey, Carl. Welcome back.
[monitor beeping steadily]
- Where am I?
- In the hospital.
You just came out
of an induced coma.
Can I ask you a question?
What happened to me?
Who are you?
Never mind that.
Tell me...Esther Doverton..
...it was all a scam, right?
You just wanted to cash
in with a rich, old broad.
- Excuse me?
- Oh, come on.
You don't need to be coy
with me. It's a great score.
Plus, she's,
uh, she's pretty good-looking..
...which is an added bonus
with these kind of scams.
Are you talking
about my wife?
Who the hell
do you think you are?
Wouldn't that be
a better question
for me to ask you,
Mr. Wysocki?
- So that's it.
- Had to end sometime.
You had a pretty good run.
And you know what?
Between you and me
I think you could squeeze
a little more nickel
out of this poor old bat.
What do you think?
Don't you talk about her
like that.
That woman is
the only good thing
that's ever happened to me.
- I love her.
- You sure about that?
Shut up and get out of here,
you son of a..
Okay, gotcha.
Told you he loved you.
'Stop.'
What are you
trying to do, kill yourself?
I'm so sorry.
I never meant to hurt you.
[instrumental music]
Got it.
Ah.
A long time ago,
that might have been a frog
or a fern or a dinosaur.
Then it died,
turned into coal..
Yeah, I know.
I did first grade geology, too.
Well, I'm just saying, it's, uh,
just compressed carbon to me.
If you want to keep it,
I never saw a thing.
What? Get outta here. I wasn't
even thinkin' about that.
Well, if you say so.
Seriously, you'd let me just
walk out of here with this?
Do you want to?
No, of course not.
I mean, yes, I'm tempted.
Okay, then.
Put it in your pocket.
This is a trap, isn't it?
Are you nuts? What do I care
about your integrity?
Oh, yeah, trap.
- Okay. Huh.
- Huh.
- Oh, uh, Grace.
- Hi.
Rigsby put something
in your pocket.
What?
Wow.
H-he's messing with you.
Oh, it's compressed carbon.
If you want to keep it...
I don't know about Rigsby,
but, uh..
I wouldn't tell a soul.
[male narrator]
'Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.'
[theme music]